# Quiz structure
quiz_data = [
    # Question 1
    {
        'question': 'What is Python?
        'options': ['Data type', 'Musical instrument', 'Snake in English', 'Programming language'],
        'correct_option': 3
    },
    # Question 2
    {
        'question': 'Which data type is used to store integers?',
        'options': ['int', 'float', 'str', 'natural'],
        'correct_option': 0
    },
    # Question 3
    {
        'question': 'How do I get data from the user?
        'options': ['get()', 'input()', 'input()', 'read()', 'cin()', 'readLine()'],
        'correct_option': 1
    },
    # Question 4
    {
        'question': 'Which function outputs something to the console?',
        'options': ['print()', 'out()', 'write()', 'log()'],
        'correct_option': 0
    },
    # Question 5
    {
        'question': 'Which library is responsible for time?
        'options': ['clock', 'localtime', 'time', 'Time'],
        'correct_option': 2
    },
    # Question 6
    {
        'question': 'How many libraries can be imported into one project?',
        'options': ['No more than 3', 'No more than 10', 'No more than 5', 'No more than 23', 'Unlimited number'],
        'correct_option': 4
    },
    # Question 7
    {
        'question': 'What does Python use the built-in enumerate() function for sequences?',
        'options': ['Determine the number of elements', 'Iterate on elements and indices', 'Sort elements by id'],
        'correct_option': 1
    },
    # Question 8
    {
        'question': 'How do I output a list of methods and attributes of object x?',
        'options': ['help(x)', 'info(x)', '?x', 'dir(x)'],
        'correct_option': 3
    },
    # Question 9
    {
        'question': 'When declaring a class using the class operator, what is written in parentheses after the class name?',
        { 'options': ['__init__', 'Class argument names', 'Class argument names', 'Superclass names', 'Child class names'],
        'correct_option': 2
    },
    # Question 10
    {
        'question': 'There is a tuple of the form T = (4, 2, 3). Which operation will cause the name T to refer to the tuple (1, 2, 3)?‚Äù?'
        'options': ['T[0] = 1', 'T = (1) + T[1:]', 'T = (1,) + T[1:]', 'T.startswith(1)'],
        'correct_option': 2
    }
]
